<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 12:07:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1175-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1175-books/</guid>
      <description>Woke up this morning and, as usual, sat down to read the Books section of The New York Times while drinking my coffee. This has become sort of a &#39;tradition&#39; for me and because of it I have been able to learn about many interesting books, some of which I would not have found out on my own. I also &#39;blame&#39; this activity to turning my nightstand into a mini-library on its own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The End For Pylyglot</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1174-end-of-pylyglot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1174-end-of-pylyglot/</guid>
      <description>Background It was around 2005 when I started doing translations for Free and Open-Source Software. Back then I was warmly welcomed to the Ubuntu family and quickly learned all there was to know about using their Rosetta online tool to translate and/or review existing translations for the Brazilian Portuguese language. I spent so much time doing it, even during working hours, that eventually I sort of &amp;quot;made a name for myself&amp;quot; and made my way up to the upper layers of the Ubuntu Community echelon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twenty Three Years</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1172-twenty-three-years-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1172-twenty-three-years-in-america/</guid>
      <description>My parents were eagerly awaiting our arrival on an early Spring morning, and when our plane finally landed after the almost 10 1/2 hours flight and we made our way to the luggage claim area, the reunion was filled with a lot of hugging, laughter and a huge sigh of relief. For someone who had spent most of their entire lives in a small and sleepy town in the East coast of Brazil, waking up and finding yourself at JFK Airport was nothing short of a major event!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running On Empty</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/running-on-empty-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/running-on-empty-/</guid>
      <description>This post has been sitting in my Drafts folder for a while now, as I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure when the right time would be to publish it. It is basically my personal reflection on the last 5 years I have worked doing translations for free and open source software (FOSS) and a few lessons I learned along the way. It is also a rant against those who took my labor for granted.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
