<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Writing a Book: Check!</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1190-writing-a-book-check/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1190-writing-a-book-check/</guid>
      <description>Growing up my dad used to tell me that there are three important milestones on a man’s life (though I feel that the same could be said about any gender):
 Plant a tree Have a child Write a book  Through my life, I have planted quite a few trees, including a lemon and papaya tree I used to treat as my imaginary friends :)
I have also had the highest honor to be the father to three amazing girls!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Quality Engineering: Tales From The Trenches</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1189-software-quality-engineering-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1189-software-quality-engineering-book/</guid>
      <description>First of all, I have to say that I absolutely love being a Quality Engineer, something that I have been doing for a living for the last 11 years of my life! During these 11 years, I have had the pleasure (yes, pleasure!) of being tossed around, torn to pieces and thrown at a lot of scary and difficult situations in the world of software testing!
Armed only with a strong desire to learn and excel at my profession, I have seen, heard and gone through a multitude of experiences, challenges, and opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gift</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1188-the-gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1188-the-gift/</guid>
      <description>It was June 8th,1974 and on a warm evening in the territory of Amapá, now a state in the northern part of Brazil, a baby boy was born. Other than being a couple of months premature, the one thing that made this birth a bit more interesting than any premature birth was the fact that this baby had its hands and feet completely bent inwards, almost fused into his arms and legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1175-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1175-books/</guid>
      <description>Woke up this morning and, as usual, sat down to read the Books section of The New York Times while drinking my coffee. This has become sort of a &#39;tradition&#39; for me and because of it I have been able to learn about many interesting books, some of which I would not have found out on my own. I also &#39;blame&#39; this activity to turning my nightstand into a mini-library on its own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The End For Pylyglot</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1174-end-of-pylyglot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1174-end-of-pylyglot/</guid>
      <description>Background It was around 2005 when I started doing translations for Free and Open-Source Software. Back then I was warmly welcomed to the Ubuntu family and quickly learned all there was to know about using their Rosetta online tool to translate and/or review existing translations for the Brazilian Portuguese language. I spent so much time doing it, even during working hours, that eventually I sort of &amp;quot;made a name for myself&amp;quot; and made my way up to the upper layers of the Ubuntu Community echelon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twenty Three Years</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1172-twenty-three-years-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1172-twenty-three-years-in-america/</guid>
      <description>My parents were eagerly awaiting our arrival on an early Spring morning, and when our plane finally landed after the almost 10 1/2 hours flight and we made our way to the luggage claim area, the reunion was filled with a lot of hugging, laughter and a huge sigh of relief. For someone who had spent most of their entire lives in a small and sleepy town in the East coast of Brazil, waking up and finding yourself at JFK Airport was nothing short of a major event!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running On Empty</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/running-on-empty-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/running-on-empty-/</guid>
      <description>This post has been sitting in my Drafts folder for a while now, as I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure when the right time would be to publish it. It is basically my personal reflection on the last 5 years I have worked doing translations for free and open source software (FOSS) and a few lessons I learned along the way. It is also a rant against those who took my labor for granted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Debian Server Setup HOWTO</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/good-debian-server-setup-howto-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/good-debian-server-setup-howto-/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this year OSNews published my article titled &amp;quot;Installing Debian Linux For The Faint Of Heart.&amp;quot; Today I came across another article dealing with the same subject. Now, I know people have hammered these types of articles to death in the net but this one sounded worth the risk of mentioning. For one thing, it covers hardening your bare-bones Debian server which, IMHO should be worth looking at no matter what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Archeologists Will Google Dig</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/cyber-archeologists-will-google-dig-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/cyber-archeologists-will-google-dig-/</guid>
      <description>Having read this yesterday on how Google has become such a major presence in our life style, today&amp;rsquo;s article in the NY Times showed me yet another facet to living in the 21st century. I can only imagine future archeologists performing &amp;ldquo;cyber-digs&amp;rdquo; in order to study civilizations from our time. Why travel to Egypt if you can uncover everything there is to know about the pyramids from the confort of your house using Google search and maps?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Picasa 2: Cool UI</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/picasa-2-cool-ui-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/picasa-2-cool-ui-/</guid>
      <description>I needed to do some image editing the other day and didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like installing anything &amp;ldquo;big and complicated&amp;rdquo; like Photoshop or PSP. Google&amp;rsquo;s Picasa software came to mind and I quickly downloaded it on my laptop. I misy tell you that I&amp;rsquo;m very impressed with user interface. Not as much with the features (which by the way are just enough for your daily crop-resize-remove red eye needs) but the looks of it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Little Penguin Wine</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/the-little-penguin-wine-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/the-little-penguin-wine-/</guid>
      <description>Almost forgot&amp;hellip; The other day I went to the public booze market and saw this little fellow:
Didn&amp;rsquo;t have a chance to taste it but if it is as good as some of the other Australian wines I&amp;rsquo;ve had and robust like Linux, then it should be great! =)
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There And Back Again</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/there-and-back-again-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/there-and-back-again-/</guid>
      <description>After driving approximately 1,014 miles over this Memorial Day weekend, I&amp;rsquo;m finally back home from Chapel Hill. Had a blast visiting my sister together with my wife and daughter. My older sister and uncle also tagged along to supposedly help out with the driving. Went to sleep at 1am on Thursday and got up at 4am!!! Managed to get there by 3pm and was completely overwhelmed by a feeling of peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living In A Movie</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/living-in-a-movie-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/living-in-a-movie-/</guid>
      <description>Kinda scary when you can relate your job to a movie:
 BOB SLYDELL Y&amp;rsquo;see, what we&amp;rsquo;re trying to do here, we&amp;rsquo;re just trying to get a feel for how people spend their day. So, if you would, would you just walk us through a typical day for you? PETER Yeah. BOB SLYDELL Great. PETER Well, I generally come in at least fifteen minutes late. I use the side door, that way Lumbergh can&amp;rsquo;t see me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About To Get Rough</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/about-to-get-rough-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/about-to-get-rough-/</guid>
      <description>Today all consultants working for my current employer received the email below (contents changed to protect the innocents):
 As the old-timers among you know, I periodically ask the IT consultants the gross annual or hourly pay you receive from your respective consultant firm. This information helps us determine the salary range and level of equity among the consultants of each work type/skill set; check that the consultant firm margins are somewhat reasonable, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s A Wireless World After All</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/its-a-wireless-world-after-all-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/its-a-wireless-world-after-all-/</guid>
      <description>Incredible! Here I am waiting outside my wife&amp;rsquo;s doctor&amp;rsquo;s office, bored out of my mind when I decide to check if anyone had left me an open Wi-Fi AP. Much to my surprise, I found 8 completely available and am bored no more! =)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Does It Mean???</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/what-does-it-mean-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/what-does-it-mean-/</guid>
      <description>What does it mean when your direct supervisor keeps asking you to do some of his tasks and you know for a fact there&amp;rsquo;s no promotion involved? I guess my biggest &amp;ldquo;beef&amp;rdquo; is the type of stuff he asks me to write about:
 What is .NET and what advantages does it offer? What are the advantages of using Microsoft Visual Source Safe (VSS)? What are the requirements for working on the code library we just purchased and have no documentation on?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Do We Get These People?</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/where-do-we-get-these-people-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/where-do-we-get-these-people-/</guid>
      <description>While typing my last post I was interrupted by a so-called &amp;ldquo;.Net Developer who just earned his PMP.&amp;rdquo; He&amp;rsquo;s been &amp;ldquo;featured&amp;rdquo; here before for asking &amp;ldquo;very intelligent questions.&amp;rdquo; =) This time he told me he had just bundled some application and given to a DBA to run it when they received an error message: Oracle[blah blah blah].dll not found!!!
 &amp;quot;So this program you wrote is trying to connect to an Oracle database?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Away From My Desk</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/away-from-my-desk-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/away-from-my-desk-/</guid>
      <description>Starting today I will be stuck attending some training class for work. These &amp;ldquo;classes&amp;rdquo; start at 9am and end at 4:30pm, all through Friday! Hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll get a chance to grab a cup of coffee in the next 5 minutes. Managed to update this blog to WordPress 1.5.1. Since this was a bux-fixing release, don&amp;rsquo;t expect to find anything changed here.
As a side note, am looking forward to some WoW playing time with Vinny tonight!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying Out Perforce</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/trying-out-perforce-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/trying-out-perforce-/</guid>
      <description>Tonight I want to take a quick break from playing WoW and install Perforce SCM System at home:
 The Perforce SCM System features comprehensive software configuration management capabilities built around a scalable client/server architecture. Requiring only TCP/IP, developers can access the Perforce Server through a variety of Perforce clients (GUIs for several platforms, Web, or Command-Line). Perforce can be deployed quickly and easily, and requires minimal administration, even for large or distributed sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Hazy Shade Of Freedom</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/a-hazy-shade-of-freedom-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/a-hazy-shade-of-freedom-/</guid>
      <description>After battling for a few days with a certain free (as in non-proxy-ed) wifi AP, I experienced approximately 5 minutes of unlimited freedom right after lunch. My friend Kelvin and I had spent a good chunk of our morning trying to figure out why the connection was dropping all the time but to no avail. I did some &amp;ldquo;googling&amp;rdquo; around and saw that some people have been complaining about the same problem but for me this only happens at this certain AP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Close Call</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/close-call-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/close-call-/</guid>
      <description>Not in a blogging mood today&amp;hellip; Got home last night at 9:30pm(!!!) and checked my messages: 1 new message! An old girl-friend crying and mumbbling about her sister (also an old good friend) having an accident&amp;hellip; broken up telephone number to call back (she must have called from a cell phone&amp;hellip; had to rewind message 2 times&amp;hellip; Call number and a guy answers&amp;hellip; After introductions (&amp;ldquo;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m an old friend of such and such&amp;hellip;&amp;quot;) learn that the sister had apparently &amp;ldquo;thrown herself out the window of her second floor apartment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beware of Crabs When Fishing</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/beware-of-crabs-when-fishing-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/beware-of-crabs-when-fishing-/</guid>
      <description>Last night I decided to work on my plan of racking up World of Warcraft hours in order to beef up my character but since my friend Vinny was busy with his own quests, I decided to try my newly learned skill: fishing! As stupid as this may sound, I never thought that fishing in a game could be so&amp;hellip; relaxing! I switched my character&amp;rsquo;s sword for a fishing pole and spent a good 15 minutes casting the line and watching the bobber.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Audioscrobbler</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/using-audioscrobbler-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/using-audioscrobbler-/</guid>
      <description>Read some posts of people talking about Audioscrobbler today and decided to see what the noise was all about.
 Audioscrobbler builds a profile of your musical taste using a plugin for your media player (Winamp, iTunes, XMMS, foobar2000, etc..). Plugins send the name of every song you play to the Audioscrobbler server, which updates your musical profile with the new song. Every person with a plugin has their own page on this site which shows their listening statistics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Night</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/game-night-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/game-night-/</guid>
      <description>Last night was my weekly night to play games with my friend Vinny. I have been playing Enemy Territory every Wednesday night since last Summer with a few cancellations here and there. Earlier this year Vinny convinced me to try World of Warcraft, a very addictive online multiplayer game. I was hooked from the start but not being able to &amp;ldquo;dedicate&amp;rdquo; to more than a couple of hours a week I eventually lost interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lynx Browser on Windows</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/lynx-browser-on-windows-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/lynx-browser-on-windows-/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;m a geek!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got Visitors? Hire a Chef!</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/got-visitors-hire-a-chef-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/got-visitors-hire-a-chef-/</guid>
      <description>Interesting...
 &amp;quot;But the best thing was the chef Nat had hired for the week, who cooked delicious crepes every morning. He even cooked, after seeing there was a Spanish guy in the crowd, some Spanish omelettes.&amp;quot;
 Once again I have solid proof that there are better ways of &amp;ldquo;team building&amp;rdquo; than what I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced so far in my short career as a developer. It used to be that the IT group of any organization ruled, getting a lot of respect and perks along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benjamin Mako Hill</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/benjamin-mako-hill-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/benjamin-mako-hill-/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s official!!! I have arranged for Benjamin Mako Hill, Debian and Ubuntu Linux package maintaner/contributer, to attend our next Northern New Jersey Meetup meeting this Monday 11th, 2005! I have asked him to talk about Ubuntu Linux and also his involvement with Debian. This should be a very interesting meeting for everyone and I urge everyone to show up! Make sure to reserve your spot so I have a good idea of how many people will be present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Satellite</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/google-satelite-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/google-satelite-/</guid>
      <description>Amazing upgrade to the already amazing Google Maps site. Don&amp;rsquo;t really know when it was implemented but you can now switch from the map view to a real satellite view, down to the street level! I can only imagine the day you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to have a live feed of traffic conditions via satellite on your web browser of choice!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Me Introduce You To My Little Friend</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/let-me-introduce-you-to-my-little-friend-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/let-me-introduce-you-to-my-little-friend-/</guid>
      <description>I was really bad over this weekend&amp;hellip; I not only had a cup of (gasp!) Star Bucks coffee but I also managed to convince my wife that we deserved a new flat LCD monitor to replace our existing 17-inch. We finally settled (well, actually I settled for it&amp;hellip; she wasn&amp;rsquo;t too thrilled about it&amp;hellip; hehe) for a 20.1-inch Sony model. Its UXGA 1600 x 1200 resolution is amazing!!! I have so much space on my screen now&amp;hellip; I also managed to update the driver for my G-Force 5200 card adding the final touch to a great system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bigger GMail</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/bigger-gmail-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/bigger-gmail-/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m really loving this &amp;ldquo;war&amp;rdquo; between Google and Yahoo, battling to see who attracts more users. I think we, the &amp;ldquo;middle man,&amp;rdquo; will only gain in the end. Today Google announced they&amp;rsquo;re increasing everyone&amp;rsquo;s gmail account to a whopping 2GB!!! Also, they&amp;rsquo;ve added the ability to write emails using rich text features, such as: Bold, Italics, Underline, Select a special font, Font Size, Font Color, Background Color, Remove Formatting, Hyperlink Text, Numbered List, Bulleted List, Indent Less, Indent More, Quote Text, Left Align, Center Align, Right Align.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>El Robot</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/el-robot-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/el-robot-/</guid>
      <description>My sister had told me about this when she called to wish us a happy Easter. She was very excited about it and thought I&amp;rsquo;d feel the same. For those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t read any &amp;ldquo;geek news&amp;rdquo; or avoid any conversations that don&amp;rsquo;t relate to music videos or movies: Wired magazine published an article in this month&amp;rsquo;s issue about &amp;ldquo;How four underdogs from the mean streets of Phoenix took on the best from M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saving The World, One Plugin AT A Time</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/saving-the-world-one-plugin-at-a-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/saving-the-world-one-plugin-at-a-time-/</guid>
      <description>Today I added the Dynamic Text Replace plugin for WordPress to my blog. I&amp;rsquo;m a bit lazy when it comes to writing and hate when I cannot do something by using the keyboard only. Or when I have to type the same thing over and over. That is why I chose to use this plugin. Dynamic Text Replace &amp;ldquo;allows you to easily pre-define text replacement template strings and allow for text to be passed in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Crystal Ship</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/the-crystal-ship-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/the-crystal-ship-/</guid>
      <description>Just as promised, here&amp;rsquo;s my screenie of netapplet and gnome-blog running on my laptop!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Alliance - March 24th, 2005</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/open-source-alliance-march-24th-2005-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/open-source-alliance-march-24th-2005-/</guid>
      <description>I completely forgot to mention about this last Thursday&amp;rsquo;s first Open Source Alliance meeting at Paramus&#39; Panera Bread. I arrived earlier than everybody else despite the really bad traffic on Route 4 West. The place was really crowded and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t set up my laptop at the &amp;ldquo;usual&amp;rdquo; place by the conference room. I ended up going to the couch by the front entrance. Armed with a hot cup of coffee I proceeded to get boot my laptop and get some internet going&amp;hellip; About 15 minutes later I realized something fishy was going on with the free wifi for I just could not get a working IP assigned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Storm On The Horizon</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/red-storm-on-the-horizon-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/red-storm-on-the-horizon-/</guid>
      <description>What a week this has been&amp;hellip; and it&amp;rsquo;s only Monday!!! After putting up with a lot of infantile abuse from my upper management things seem to be heading South. I used to feel that the entire organization was plotting against me and wondered if it was just me. But now, I have definite confirmation that my sanity is still somewhat intact! My new co-worker (and I think she was also hired to be my supervisor) has been experiencing all the abuse herself for a few weeks now and seems to be in the brink of walking out of here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Help Guy</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/ubuntu-help-guy-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/ubuntu-help-guy-/</guid>
      <description>Lately I have found myself hanging out at #ubuntu on irc.freenode.org, mostly listening and lending a helping hand whenver I can. It sort of reminds me of what I think Open Source and Community really means! I have personally gotten insulted in the past by some pretty lame IRC users who assume that everyone is an idiot and who can&amp;rsquo;t say anything helpfull but repeat &amp;ldquo;rtfm&amp;rdquo; to every enquire. But I will not go off on a tangent here and rant about all those &amp;ldquo;newbie basher&amp;rdquo; loosers out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Meetup - March 14, 2005</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/linux-meetup-march-14-2005-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/linux-meetup-march-14-2005-/</guid>
      <description>This past Monday I hosted the monthly Northern New Jersey Linux Meetup at Panera Bread. It is the 7th meeting I have organized ever since taken over the group back in September 2004. I managed to get there earlier than usual and took advantage of the extra time to write down some ideas I had for a new pet project of mine and get some good coffee. One hour later some of the frequent attendees arrived.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petri Dish Children</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/petri-dish-children-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/petri-dish-children-/</guid>
      <description>My daughter is very ill. Actually, she&amp;rsquo;s been ill for a few days now with very high fever and coughing coupled with a persistent runny nose. I had to take Wednesday off from work so I could bring her to her doctor but it turned out to be a complete waste of time. He even performed an on-site strep throat test to see if that was the problem but the results were inconclusive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Saga Continues</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/the-saga-continues-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/the-saga-continues-/</guid>
      <description>My personal quest of gathering as much information as possible on the requirements to enroll into a PhD program at the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill continued last Friday. I was up and early for my appointments at the Department of Computer Science considering I went to sleep really late the previous night. It was my sister&amp;rsquo;s birthday so I took her out to the movies and a late dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tar Heel Dreaming</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/tar-heel-dreaming-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/tar-heel-dreaming-/</guid>
      <description>Arrived here in North Carolina last night at the Raleigh-Durham airport. My younger sister was waiting for me and as soon as we picked up my luggage we headed to her apartment in Chapel Hill. Woke up early today and went to my first (and only) meeting with the chair of the School of Information and Library Science at UNC. My sister had set up the meeting for me and I must admit I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too sure if I wanted to spend the time to talk to someone from a department that had the word &amp;ldquo;library&amp;rdquo; in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going To The Country</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/going-to-the-country-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/going-to-the-country-/</guid>
      <description>The day I fly to North Carolina has finally arrived. I&amp;rsquo;m extremelly excited about this trip for it could be the kick in ass I need to get back on track with my goals. I&amp;rsquo;ll be staying at my younger sister&amp;rsquo;s apartment which I believe is near the UNC&#39;s Chapel Hill campus. She&#39;s already scheduled 4 interviews with the chairs of 4 different departments and I have just emailed her to try to get me 2 more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tar Heel Wanna Be</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/tar-heel-wanna-be-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/tar-heel-wanna-be-/</guid>
      <description>This Wednesday I embark on what may be the most important trip of my life: I&amp;rsquo;ll be visiting and interviewing with the chairs of several different departments at the North Carolina Univertsity with the objective of gathering information for my possible come back to the academic world. It&amp;rsquo;s been almost 8 years since I graduated from Pace University and my plans of earning a PhD/MD diploma have taken a major detour.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
