<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>django on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/django/</link>
    <description>Recent content in django on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/django/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pylyglot: Open Source Translation Search</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/pylyglot-open-source-translation-search-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/pylyglot-open-source-translation-search-/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I wrote about Pylyglot, my translation searching tool that I use whenever I translate open source applications. Have not heard about Pylyglot? Read the About page for more info!
The reasons for the long hiatus are too many to enumerate, but suffice to say that the project is very much alive and I intend to keep updating the translations database as often as possible.
So, what&amp;rsquo;s new?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django DevKit Appliance 1.3.1</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/django-devkit-appliance-1-3-1-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/django-devkit-appliance-1-3-1-/</guid>
      <description>I rebuilt the appliance to use the latest Django 1.3.1 release to deliver the security fixes found in the previous version. There are also several other updated packages included.
If you want to play with this appliance, feel free to download it in the following formats:
 Django DevKit Raw Filesystem x86 (390 MB - SHA1: 3ae0ab73477be3308011735aac5b33908700a82d) Django DevKit Raw Filesystem x86_64 (411 MB - SHA1: 3fb040a9b48b0dc248e5424271d4ea9274605530) Django DevKit ISO x86 (517 MB - SHA1: 88d5f1065bf5646d7cd952e8ccac435a40176fef) Django DevKit ISO x86_64 (537 MB - SHA1: cee9f5f584261d69baca09efeb58278d23cab410)  Speaking of Raw Filesystem images, here&amp;rsquo;s how I currently use it with QEMU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django DevKit Appliance 1.3</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/django-devkit-appliance-1-3-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/django-devkit-appliance-1-3-/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I pimped my Django Dev Kit Appliance, mostly because I have been really busy with work, projects and my kid&amp;rsquo;s end of the school year. Anyhow, I rebuilt the appliance to use the latest Django 1.3 release plus several other updated packages such as git and mercurial. I have also stopped building Amazon EC2 images and will from now on only provide ISOs and Raw Filesystem images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing: Foresight based Django Developer Kit Appliance RC1</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/announcing-foresight-based-django-developer-kit-applianc-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/announcing-foresight-based-django-developer-kit-applianc-/</guid>
      <description>If you remember one of my last posts, I wanted to eventually migrate my Django Developer Kit Appliance to use Foresight Linux as the underlying operating system&amp;hellip; and I am proud to announce that I have made huge strides toward this goal!
Thanks to the guidance of some fellow rPathians, I managed to get an almost ready for production Django 1.2.3 + PostgreSQL 8.4 + Python 2.6.2 and lots of Django modules and latest versions for Git, Mercurial, Bzr, and Subversion ready to be used!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Devel Kit Appliance 1.2.3</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/django-devel-kit-appliance-1-2-3-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/django-devel-kit-appliance-1-2-3-/</guid>
      <description>No, this is not a repeat from yesterday&amp;rsquo;s post. Turns out there was another security release for Django yesterday (thanks Zygmunt for the heads up), so here&amp;rsquo;s the release of Django Developer Kit Appliance 1.2.3.
As always, choose from the following image types:
 Amazon EC2 AMI Large (ami-ba996cd3) Amazon EC2 AMI Small (ami-a0996cc9) ISO x86 (SHA1 11811571ee8f8f2a0d7778c9e4275060de73f271) ISO x86_64 (SHA1 065b1c5dfa410cffeec9950d577cddd15f369bad) Raw Filesystem x86 (SHA1 141427d7c84449ccc7eacbee7d527b8ba6f7ca48) Raw Filesystem x86_64 (SHA1 482ecbbd2c177e3fdc33b18dc0ee65c83d681956) VMware ESX x86 (SHA1 10757fd1f0ec119fe236f3402bf38dfde25cb40a) VMware ESX x86 OVF 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Developer Kit Appliance 1.2.2</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/django-developer-kit-appliance-1-2-2-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/django-developer-kit-appliance-1-2-2-/</guid>
      <description>Today I&amp;rsquo;m releasing my Django Developer Kit Appliance 1.2.2 due to the recent security release of Django 1.2.2. Other than a newer version of Django, you&amp;rsquo;ll also get newer versions of several packages already included by default in the appliance.
I have been working hard (time permitting, off course) on migrating the appliance to a slim Foresight Linux base in order to upgrade the underlying python from 2.4 to latest 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review: Django 1.2 E-Commerce</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/review-django-1-2-e-commerce-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/review-django-1-2-e-commerce-/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Django 1.2 E-Commerce&amp;rdquo; starts with a very ambitious goal: design, develop and deploy a functional ecommerce web site for the fictional CranStore.com company. Sounds great, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?
I started flipping through the usual introductory pages explaining what Django is and why use it for a project like this. It was all fairly brief which already led me to believe that knowledge of Django&amp;rsquo;s inner works and basic setup and configuration was required to follow along.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
