<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>gnome on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/gnome/</link>
    <description>Recent content in gnome on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/gnome/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Emacs &#43; Rope for Python Development</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/emacs-rope-for-python-development-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/emacs-rope-for-python-development-/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is more of a note for myself than a proper tutorial or howto, so I make no promises that this will work for you. The setup used through this post was a Mac OS laptop upgraded to the very latest version of the OS.
Ever since I started doing Python development using Emacs, I have unsuccessfully tried to configure Rope, &amp;ldquo;a python refactoring library&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; until last Friday. Turns out I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too far off the mark during the many iterations I went through to get it done, but the following post was tremendously helpful to me: http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME 3.0, Banshee 2.0 and Foresight Linux</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/gnome-3-0-banshee-2-0-and-foresight-linux-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/gnome-3-0-banshee-2-0-and-foresight-linux-/</guid>
      <description>First off, congratulations to everyone involved in the release of GNOME 3.0! In the past, my contributions were mostly related to translating applications to Brazilian Portuguese, but my role on that front was very minimal this time and consisted of a handful of translations and several commits of the awesome work done by others. Most of my contributions for 3.0 are related to the work I do for the GNOME Foundation Board of Directors, but I won&amp;rsquo;t bore you to tears!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME 3.0 Translations</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/gnome-3-0-translations-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/gnome-3-0-translations-/</guid>
      <description>Hey, are you feverishly working on the translation for the upcoming GNOME 3.0 release? Do you find yourself often wondering how a certain word was translated across the entire desktop applications? Well, I do and this is why I developed Pylyglot, a Django-driven localization tool that let&amp;rsquo;s you search for a word and see how it has been translated for a given language. The plan is to have fresh data straight from the GNOME git repositories every Monday for now, eventually switching to a more frequent update schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Summit 2010: Day 2</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/boston-summit-2010-day-2-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/boston-summit-2010-day-2-/</guid>
      <description>I got back from the Boston Summit around 22:00 Sunday evening and by the time I arrived home from the airport I was too tired to write up a blog post. Then Monday morning came and after all the meetings, work and side projects, I decided to spend some quality time with my kids, as I had not seen them since Friday evening.
The second day was very busy and full of things to do and interesting discussions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Summit 2010: Day 1</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/boston-summit-2010-day-1-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/boston-summit-2010-day-1-/</guid>
      <description>Finally sat down to write down about my first day attending the Boston Summit 2010 but Paul [1] and Jason[1,2,3] already beat me to it. From my perspective, it was really nice to finally meet face to face with some of my fellow Board members and make new friends!
I want to thank Novell for hosting us at their office for our Board meeting (there should be a picture of us posing in front of a Novell logo) and our gracious host.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Me Hear Your Voices</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/let-me-hear-your-voices-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/let-me-hear-your-voices-/</guid>
      <description>This weekend I&amp;rsquo;ll be attending my first Boston Summit, courtesy of theGNOME Travel Committee! It will also be my very first time meeting my fellow members of the GNOME Foundation Board of Directors, which makes me very excited!
I wanted to ask you, readers of my blog, what kind of questions would you like me to ask on your behalf? Do you have any constructive comments or feedback for us? What are the areas you feel that we should invest more of our resources on and which ones should we spend less?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Planning a GNOME 3.0 Launch Party?</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/are-you-planning-a-gnome-3-0-launch-party-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/are-you-planning-a-gnome-3-0-launch-party-/</guid>
      <description>In order to promote the GNOME 3.0 launch and spread the idea amongst the GNOME community members, I&amp;rsquo;m sharing the following message! Please translate it and share it with your friends and help us organize the biggest GNOME Launch ever!
Dear GNOME friends,
The GNOME.Asia committee is working on making a big launch party (whichÂ includes a 5 days hackfest) to celebrate, promote and work on the GNOMEÂ 3.0 release as part of our effort to promote GNOME in Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Summit 2010</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/boston-summit-2010-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/boston-summit-2010-/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m also coming to the Boston Summit for the first time! I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to hanging out with my fellow Board members, meeting some of them for the very first time. I&amp;rsquo;m also looking forward to attending the Snowy Hackfest and other sessions related to GNOME 3.0!
Think you can join us? Take a look at the GNOME Foundation blog for more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
