<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>brazil on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/brazil/</link>
    <description>Recent content in brazil on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/brazil/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Gift</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1188-the-gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1188-the-gift/</guid>
      <description>It was June 8th,1974 and on a warm evening in the territory of Amapá, now a state in the northern part of Brazil, a baby boy was born. Other than being a couple of months premature, the one thing that made this birth a bit more interesting than any premature birth was the fact that this baby had its hands and feet completely bent inwards, almost fused into his arms and legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back from the Tropics</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/back-from-the-tropics-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/back-from-the-tropics-/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I last posted anything new. That&amp;rsquo;s because I took some time off from work and headed down to my old stomping grounds&amp;hellip; Brazil! It had been 5 years since I visited my friends and relatives and since I couldn&amp;rsquo;t make it to GUADEC and take my family on vacation at the same time, we hoped on a straight flight to Rio de Janeiro from Charlotte&#39;s international airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bota água no feijão!</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/bota-agua-no-feijao-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/bota-agua-no-feijao-/</guid>
      <description>Depois de quase 5 anos estarei voltando à pátria amada! É isso aí! Como não vai dar para ir na Holanda na conferência GUADEC 2010 (muuuuito caro) este ano, vou então com a família toda para o Brasil.
Vou ficar no norte do Espirito Santo por quase 2 semanas, vegetando e apresentando os primos, tios, tias, avós, etc para a minha filha mais nova (a minha esposa e filha mais velha já estiveram no Brasil antes).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
