<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>foresight on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/foresight/</link>
    <description>Recent content in foresight on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/foresight/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PackageKit Progress on Foresight</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/packagekit-progress-on-foresight-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/packagekit-progress-on-foresight-/</guid>
      <description>For a while Foresight Linux users had no graphical interface for managing their systems packages and/or updates, mainly because the development for the conary backend fell out of scope and our radar (this is a nicer way to say that we didn&amp;rsquo;t have someone to maintain it). But thanks to the work of zodman, jesse and others PackageKit is making its way back to our desktop.
[caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_1395&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;296&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Available updates&amp;rdquo;][/caption]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME 3.0, Banshee 2.0 and Foresight Linux</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/gnome-3-0-banshee-2-0-and-foresight-linux-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/gnome-3-0-banshee-2-0-and-foresight-linux-/</guid>
      <description>First off, congratulations to everyone involved in the release of GNOME 3.0! In the past, my contributions were mostly related to translating applications to Brazilian Portuguese, but my role on that front was very minimal this time and consisted of a handful of translations and several commits of the awesome work done by others. Most of my contributions for 3.0 are related to the work I do for the GNOME Foundation Board of Directors, but I won&amp;rsquo;t bore you to tears!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now That You&#39;ve Found Love What Are You Gonna Do?</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/now-that-youve-found-love-what-are-you-gonna-do-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/now-that-youve-found-love-what-are-you-gonna-do-/</guid>
      <description>Now that you have downloaded and installed the latest Foresight Linux 2.5 release, here are a couple of things you may want to do:
  Update Your System: Since Foresight has a rolling release schedule, we already have updates for you, including and newer MPlayer with support for Blue-Ray!  Run sudo conary updateall
   Install Chromium web browser: Try this pretty cool web browser made by Google.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foresight Linux 2.5.0!</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/foresight-linux-2-5-0-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/foresight-linux-2-5-0-/</guid>
      <description>At last, after a long hiatus, I can shout out for the whole world to hear: Foresight Linux 2.5.0 is out and about! This is our first official release in almost 2 years (2.1.1 was released May 15th, 2009!!!) and it is filled to the brim with the very latest stable applications out there!
A lot of work, sweat, and tears by a lot of different people went into getting this release out the door, and to all of you out there who stood by us through thick and thin, I thank you and salute you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foresight Linux 2.5.0 Release Candidate Galore!</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/foresight-linux-2-5-0-release-candidate-galore-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/foresight-linux-2-5-0-release-candidate-galore-/</guid>
      <description>It is with great pleasure that I announce the release of Foresight 2.5.0 RC! This time, we have updated images for GNOME, Xfce and KDE! Things are shaping up quite nicely and thanks to all the feedback we&amp;rsquo;ve received from our users, we should be releasing our GA images pretty soon!
Well known for being a desktop operating system featuring an intuitive user interface and a showcase of the latest desktop software, this new release brings you the latest GNOME 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Foresight Linux 2.5.0 ALPHA 2 GNOME Edition</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/announcing-foresight-linux-2-5-0-alpha-2-gnome-edition-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/announcing-foresight-linux-2-5-0-alpha-2-gnome-edition-/</guid>
      <description>Who said that lightening doesn&amp;rsquo;t strike twice on the same spot? I&amp;rsquo;m proud to announce the release of Foresight Linux 2.5.0 ALPHA 2 GNOME Edition!
Once again, this alpha release is from our QA branch, and is intended mostly to receive feedback on brand new installs from end-users, specially in relation to the overall behavior of X.org on first boot! Obviously, if you&amp;rsquo;re already running Foresight Linux 2.5.0 ALPHA1, simply update your system from the command line: *sudo conary updateall*</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Because Your Distro Should Be Cool!</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/because-your-distro-should-be-cool-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/because-your-distro-should-be-cool-/</guid>
      <description>It is with my Community Manager hat and as a Linux enthusiast that I bring you this post about the Foresight Linux distribution, literally born and brewed where I work and filled to the brim with the technology developed at rPath. However, this is not yet another article about yet another Linux distribution with arguments about how great it is compared to other popular ones out there. No siree Bob! In fact, if you are happy with the platform or distribution that you are running, then kudos to you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Foresight Linux 2.5.0 ALPHA 1 GNOME Edition</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/announcing-foresight-linux-2-5-0-alpha-1-gnome-edition-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/announcing-foresight-linux-2-5-0-alpha-1-gnome-edition-/</guid>
      <description>After a very, very, very long time I can finally announce another Foresight Linux release! We have gone through a lot of changes and it took us a while to rebuild our developer/maintainer/user base, but here we are! The goal is to go back to having a rolling release schedule and keep bringing the latest and greatest mix of GNOME and applications!
[caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_1284&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;300&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Localized (Swedish) screenshot of Foresight Linux&amp;rdquo;][/caption]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking For a Graphic Designer</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/looking-for-a-graphic-designer-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/looking-for-a-graphic-designer-/</guid>
      <description>The Foresight Linux team is looking for a good graphic designer to help them with a splash screen!
**Foresight Linux,**a desktop operating system featuring an intuitive user interface and a showcase of the latest desktop software&amp;quot; is now gearing for a major release with all the latest and greatest applications out there!
Would you like to see your art work distributed and displayed whenever someone boots Foresight Linux? If so, please drop me a line for more information!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing: Foresight based Django Developer Kit Appliance RC1</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/announcing-foresight-based-django-developer-kit-applianc-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/announcing-foresight-based-django-developer-kit-applianc-/</guid>
      <description>If you remember one of my last posts, I wanted to eventually migrate my Django Developer Kit Appliance to use Foresight Linux as the underlying operating system&amp;hellip; and I am proud to announce that I have made huge strides toward this goal!
Thanks to the guidance of some fellow rPathians, I managed to get an almost ready for production Django 1.2.3 + PostgreSQL 8.4 + Python 2.6.2 and lots of Django modules and latest versions for Git, Mercurial, Bzr, and Subversion ready to be used!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Devel Kit Appliance 1.2.3</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/django-devel-kit-appliance-1-2-3-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/django-devel-kit-appliance-1-2-3-/</guid>
      <description>No, this is not a repeat from yesterday&amp;rsquo;s post. Turns out there was another security release for Django yesterday (thanks Zygmunt for the heads up), so here&amp;rsquo;s the release of Django Developer Kit Appliance 1.2.3.
As always, choose from the following image types:
 Amazon EC2 AMI Large (ami-ba996cd3) Amazon EC2 AMI Small (ami-a0996cc9) ISO x86 (SHA1 11811571ee8f8f2a0d7778c9e4275060de73f271) ISO x86_64 (SHA1 065b1c5dfa410cffeec9950d577cddd15f369bad) Raw Filesystem x86 (SHA1 141427d7c84449ccc7eacbee7d527b8ba6f7ca48) Raw Filesystem x86_64 (SHA1 482ecbbd2c177e3fdc33b18dc0ee65c83d681956) VMware ESX x86 (SHA1 10757fd1f0ec119fe236f3402bf38dfde25cb40a) VMware ESX x86 OVF 1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
