<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>boston summit on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/boston-summit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in boston summit on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/boston-summit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Boston Summit 2010: Day 2</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/boston-summit-2010-day-2-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/boston-summit-2010-day-2-/</guid>
      <description>I got back from the Boston Summit around 22:00 Sunday evening and by the time I arrived home from the airport I was too tired to write up a blog post. Then Monday morning came and after all the meetings, work and side projects, I decided to spend some quality time with my kids, as I had not seen them since Friday evening.
The second day was very busy and full of things to do and interesting discussions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Summit 2010: Day 1</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/boston-summit-2010-day-1-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/boston-summit-2010-day-1-/</guid>
      <description>Finally sat down to write down about my first day attending the Boston Summit 2010 but Paul [1] and Jason[1,2,3] already beat me to it. From my perspective, it was really nice to finally meet face to face with some of my fellow Board members and make new friends!
I want to thank Novell for hosting us at their office for our Board meeting (there should be a picture of us posing in front of a Novell logo) and our gracious host.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Me Hear Your Voices</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/let-me-hear-your-voices-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/let-me-hear-your-voices-/</guid>
      <description>This weekend I&amp;rsquo;ll be attending my first Boston Summit, courtesy of theGNOME Travel Committee! It will also be my very first time meeting my fellow members of the GNOME Foundation Board of Directors, which makes me very excited!
I wanted to ask you, readers of my blog, what kind of questions would you like me to ask on your behalf? Do you have any constructive comments or feedback for us? What are the areas you feel that we should invest more of our resources on and which ones should we spend less?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Summit 2010</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/boston-summit-2010-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/boston-summit-2010-/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m also coming to the Boston Summit for the first time! I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to hanging out with my fellow Board members, meeting some of them for the very first time. I&amp;rsquo;m also looking forward to attending the Snowy Hackfest and other sessions related to GNOME 3.0!
Think you can join us? Take a look at the GNOME Foundation blog for more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
