<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rpath, red hat on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/rpath-red-hat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rpath, red hat on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/rpath-red-hat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Starting a New Chapter: To Infinity, and Beyond!</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/starting-a-new-chapter-to-infinity-and-beyond-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/starting-a-new-chapter-to-infinity-and-beyond-/</guid>
      <description>Last October I celebrated a couple of milestones in my life:
 5 years living in North Carolina; 2 years since I bought my first house; 11 years married to my wife; 5 years working for rPath;  Needless to say, each one of those milestones were very important to me as they mark important decision points in my life! Every single one of them changed my life for the better and I can&amp;rsquo;t help but feel blessed that I have so many things to look forward to at end of the year that remind me how lucky I have been!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Um Novo Capítulo: To Infinity, and Beyond!</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/um-novo-capitulo-to-infinity-and-beyond-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/um-novo-capitulo-to-infinity-and-beyond-/</guid>
      <description>Outubro do ano passado eu comemorei alguns marcos na minha vida:
 5 anos morando na Carolina do Norte; 2 anos desde que eu comprei minha primeira casa; 11 anos casado com minha esposa; 5 anos trabalhando para rPath;  Te garanto que cada um desses marcos foram muito importantes para mim, já que marcam decisões importante na minha vida! Cada um deles mudou a minha vida para melhor e eu me sinto abençoado por ter tantas coisas para celebrar no final do ano que me fazem lembrar o quão sortudo eu tenho sido!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
