<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>automation on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/automation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in automation on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Writing a Book: Check!</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1190-writing-a-book-check/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1190-writing-a-book-check/</guid>
      <description>Growing up my dad used to tell me that there are three important milestones on a man’s life (though I feel that the same could be said about any gender):
 Plant a tree Have a child Write a book  Through my life, I have planted quite a few trees, including a lemon and papaya tree I used to treat as my imaginary friends :)
I have also had the highest honor to be the father to three amazing girls!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Quality Engineering: Tales From The Trenches</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1189-software-quality-engineering-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1189-software-quality-engineering-book/</guid>
      <description>First of all, I have to say that I absolutely love being a Quality Engineer, something that I have been doing for a living for the last 11 years of my life! During these 11 years, I have had the pleasure (yes, pleasure!) of being tossed around, torn to pieces and thrown at a lot of scary and difficult situations in the world of software testing!
Armed only with a strong desire to learn and excel at my profession, I have seen, heard and gone through a multitude of experiences, challenges, and opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
