<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rpath, north carolina, new jersey on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/rpath-north-carolina-new-jersey/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rpath, north carolina, new jersey on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/rpath-north-carolina-new-jersey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Veni, Vidi, Vici</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/veni-vidi-vici-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/veni-vidi-vici-/</guid>
      <description>Gracas a uma conexao de wireless perto de minha casa, posso escrever uma mensagem curta e breve sobre o que tem acontecido com minha vida pessoal e profisional. Por 2 semanas fiquei viajando de New York/New Jersey para North Carolina, e vice-versa, fazendo entrevistas de trabalho e procurando por uma nova vida para minha familia. Foram dias muito dificeis e e emocionais para mim, e foram varias as vezes que eu pensei em desistir e voltar para casa (New Jersey) e procurar um trabalho mediocre, mas que pudesse pagar as minhas contas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Following the Right Path</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/following-the-right-path-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/following-the-right-path-/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I last blogged but my life has been pretty hectic for the last 2 weeks. I have spent more time flying from NY to Raleigh/Durham than actually anywhere else. The airports at JFK, LGA, and RDU had strangely started to feel &amp;ldquo;confortable&amp;rdquo; and I could pretty much tell anyone where the best spots were for the wi-fi.
Well, got to meet a lot of interesting people, and better yet, had a few job interviews along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
