<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>books on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in books on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>On Reading and writing</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1184-on-reading-and-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1184-on-reading-and-writing/</guid>
      <description>This week I started reading On Writing: A Memoir of the Craft by Stephen King, a book that has been mentioned a few times by people I usually interview for my weekly podcast as something that is both inspiring and has had a major impact on their lives and careers. After the third or forth time someone mentioned I finally broke down and got myself a copy at the local bookstore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End of Year - 2015</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1182-2015-end-of-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1182-2015-end-of-year/</guid>
      <description>Another year has gone by and I guess it is time to review the things I set out to do and grade myself on how well (or poorly) I fared. Here are some of my goals for 2015:
Read 70 Books Grade: PASS
Even though I had a very, very busy year at work, with many releases of Red Hat Satellite 5 and Red Hat Satellite 6 shipped to our customers, I managed to surpass my goal of reading 70 books, finishing the year with a whopping 79 books read!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2014 in Book Covers</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1177-year-in-book-covers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1177-year-in-book-covers/</guid>
      <description>For my last post of 2014 I wanted to show, with pictures, the books I read and spent so much time with this year.
Back in January of 2014 I set out to read 30 books as part of my Reading Challenge. I wanted to focus on reading Brazilian authors early on as I felt that I really needed to learn more about Brazilian literature and this time, read books for fun and not because I was told to back when I was much younger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1175-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1175-books/</guid>
      <description>Woke up this morning and, as usual, sat down to read the Books section of The New York Times while drinking my coffee. This has become sort of a &#39;tradition&#39; for me and because of it I have been able to learn about many interesting books, some of which I would not have found out on my own. I also &#39;blame&#39; this activity to turning my nightstand into a mini-library on its own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alternatives to NY Times\&#39; Book section</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/alternatives-to-ny-times-book-section-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/alternatives-to-ny-times-book-section-/</guid>
      <description>The NY Times&#39; restriction of 10 articles/month for non-subscribers, online viewers means I won&#39;t be reading their Books section anymore. It sort of became a good habit for me and something I look forward to on Sunday mornings: as I drink my coffee and enjoy some peace and quietness as the kids are still asleep, I enjoy catching up with the latest books and reviews. This weekend ritual usually ends with a trip down to the public library with the whole family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procura-se: Irani de Castro</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/procura-se-irani-de-castro-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/procura-se-irani-de-castro-/</guid>
      <description>Depois de ter gravado mais de 9 episódios do Castálio Podcast (se você ainda não escutou, não sabe o que está acontecendo), e conversar sobre os acontecimentos, músicas, livros e filmes que moldaram a vida dos meus convidados, comecei a meditar sobre alguns dos livros que eu curtia ler quando garoto. Quando eu ainda morava no Brasil, nós tínhamos uma biblioteca bem variada na minha casa, com livro para tudo quanto é gosto&amp;hellip; mas quando me mudei para os Estados Unidos em 1991 (para ler um pouco mais sobre esta história, leia a minha coluna na edição 25 da revista Espírito Livre) eu tive de deixar tudo para trás para trazer somente o que cabia na mala (até parece aquela música do Engenheiros do Hawaii).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Expo America 2011</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-expo-america-2011-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-expo-america-2011-/</guid>
      <description>Taking a day off tomorrow to fly to NYC with my oldest daughter so we can both attend this year&amp;rsquo;s Book Expo America (BEA) at the Javits Center. We&amp;rsquo;re both very excited about this chance of seeing so many books and the possibility of meeting some of the authors, such as Mo Willems! Unfortunately I&amp;rsquo;m going to miss meeting James Dashner as he&amp;rsquo;s scheduled to give out sample chapters of his upcoming book only on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Stories of Your Life: and Others</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-review-stories-of-your-life-and-others-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-review-stories-of-your-life-and-others-/</guid>
      <description>*Disclaimer: My book reviews are my own impressions from my daily readings and are by no means &amp;ldquo;sponsored&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;influenced&amp;rdquo; by any company, organization or individuals. I don&amp;rsquo;t even get money through any referral program, so rest assured that my review is not biased. If you do, however, want me to review a book for your company or organization, feel free to contact me via the comments section and we can work something out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Emblem Divide</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-review-emblem-divide-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-review-emblem-divide-/</guid>
      <description>*Disclaimer: My book reviews are my own impressions from my daily readings and are by no means &amp;ldquo;sponsored&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;influenced&amp;rdquo; by any company, organization or individuals. I don&amp;rsquo;t even get money through any referral program, so rest assured that my review is not biased. If you do, however, want me to review a book for your company or organization, feel free to contact me via the comments section and we can work something out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Mockingjay</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-review-mockingjay-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-review-mockingjay-/</guid>
      <description>*Disclaimer: My book reviews are my own impressions from my daily readings and are by no means &amp;ldquo;sponsored&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;influenced&amp;rdquo; by any company, organization or individuals. I don&amp;rsquo;t even get money through any referral program, so rest assured that my review is not biased. If you do, however, want me to review a book for your company or organization, feel free to contact me via the comments section and we can work something out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Catching Fire</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-review-catching-fire-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-review-catching-fire-/</guid>
      <description>*Disclaimer: My book reviews are my own impressions from my daily readings and are by no means &amp;ldquo;sponsored&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;influenced&amp;rdquo; by any company, organization or individuals. I don&amp;rsquo;t even get money through any referral program, so rest assured that my review is not biased. If you do, however, want me to review a book for your company or organization, feel free to contact me via the comments section and we can work something out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Hunger Games</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-review-the-hunger-games-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-review-the-hunger-games-/</guid>
      <description>*Disclaimer: My book reviews are my own impressions from my daily readings and are by no means &amp;ldquo;sponsored&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;influenced&amp;rdquo; by any company, organization or individuals. I don&amp;rsquo;t even get money through any referral program, so rest assured that my review is not biased. If you do, however, want me to review a book for your company or organization, feel free to contact me via the comments section and we can work something out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindle</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/kindle-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/kindle-/</guid>
      <description>Over the holidays I got a second-hand Kindle DX from my sister. As I have been doing some serious reading these last couple of years, an EBook reader was something that both excited and scared me at the same time. Let me explain.
Being able to carry several books, often pretty thick and heavy, in one simple and light device has its advantages. Add to that the massive number of free EBooks and regular plain text books available on web sites such as the Internet Archive, Open Library, Project Gutenberg, and all of a sudden we&amp;rsquo;re talking about having your own private and portable library on the go!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>31 Books, 13360 Pages and Counting</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/31-books-13360-pages-and-counting-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/31-books-13360-pages-and-counting-/</guid>
      <description>One of my New Year&amp;rsquo;s resolution for 2010 was the ambitious goal of reading one book for every week of the year! In other words, to read a total of 52 books for 2010! I knew that it would be very hard to complete this resolution without cheating and choosing thin books but I figured: &amp;ldquo;Aim for the moon, that way, even if you miss you&amp;rsquo;ll still be amongst the stars!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Thrilling Adventures of Lovelace and Babbage</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/the-thrilling-adventures-of-lovelace-and-babbage-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/the-thrilling-adventures-of-lovelace-and-babbage-/</guid>
      <description>Spent a good chunk of my free time reading all 9 (out of 10) parts of Lovelace and Babbage Vs The Organist this weekend! I don&amp;rsquo;t know where to begin to describe how incredibly awesome this comic is! The graphics, the clever writing and jokes, even the sometimes absurd plot twists all combine for delivering a fantastic, fun reading experience!
I highly recommend that you read at least a few episodes and allow yourself to wander around the many links and tidbits about Charles Babbage, Ada Lovelace, Quasiamicable Pair, musical instruments, math and many other items in the notes section!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Python 3 Object Oriented Programming</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-review-python-3-object-oriented-programming-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-review-python-3-object-oriented-programming-/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t claim to have looked hard for a Python book on object oriented programming (OOP) but I was immediately attracted to the title of this book. Sure, you can find small tutorials here and there about some specific facet of OOP but I don&amp;rsquo;t recall ever reading something that covers designing public interfaces using abstraction, encapsulation, etc, etc with good and practical examples! If you have, please drop me a link in the comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review: Django 1.2 E-Commerce</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/review-django-1-2-e-commerce-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/review-django-1-2-e-commerce-/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Django 1.2 E-Commerce&amp;rdquo; starts with a very ambitious goal: design, develop and deploy a functional ecommerce web site for the fictional CranStore.com company. Sounds great, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?
I started flipping through the usual introductory pages explaining what Django is and why use it for a project like this. It was all fairly brief which already led me to believe that knowledge of Django&amp;rsquo;s inner works and basic setup and configuration was required to follow along.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Shopping Spree</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-shopping-spree-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/book-shopping-spree-/</guid>
      <description>Added these books to my personal collection&amp;hellip; These are used and even though I feel that I know some of it already, I figured they could be usefull. Should arrive by the end of the week&amp;hellip;
 Expert C# Business Objects Beginning ASP.Net 1.1 in C#:: From Novice To Professional Pro ASP.NET 1.1 in C#: From Professional to Expert Beginning VB .NET 1.1 Databases: From Novice to Professional Beginning C# Objects: From Concepts to Code  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
