<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>books on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in books on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>On Reading and writing</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1184-on-reading-and-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1184-on-reading-and-writing/</guid>
      <description>This week I started reading On Writing: A Memoir of the Craft by Stephen King, a book that has been mentioned a few times by people I usually interview for my weekly podcast as something that is both inspiring and has had a major impact on their lives and careers. After the third or forth time someone mentioned I finally broke down and got myself a copy at the local bookstore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End of Year - 2015</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1182-2015-end-of-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1182-2015-end-of-year/</guid>
      <description>Another year has gone by and I guess it is time to review the things I set out to do and grade myself on how well (or poorly) I fared. Here are some of my goals for 2015:
Read 70 Books Grade: PASS
Even though I had a very, very busy year at work, with many releases of Red Hat Satellite 5 and Red Hat Satellite 6 shipped to our customers, I managed to surpass my goal of reading 70 books, finishing the year with a whopping 79 books read!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2014 in Book Covers</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1177-year-in-book-covers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1177-year-in-book-covers/</guid>
      <description>For my last post of 2014 I wanted to show, with pictures, the books I read and spent so much time with this year.
Back in January of 2014 I set out to read 30 books as part of my Reading Challenge. I wanted to focus on reading Brazilian authors early on as I felt that I really needed to learn more about Brazilian literature and this time, read books for fun and not because I was told to back when I was much younger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1175-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/1175-books/</guid>
      <description>Woke up this morning and, as usual, sat down to read the Books section of The New York Times while drinking my coffee. This has become sort of a &#39;tradition&#39; for me and because of it I have been able to learn about many interesting books, some of which I would not have found out on my own. I also &#39;blame&#39; this activity to turning my nightstand into a mini-library on its own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alternatives to NY Times\&#39; Book section</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/alternatives-to-ny-times-book-section-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/alternatives-to-ny-times-book-section-/</guid>
      <description>The NY Times&#39; restriction of 10 articles/month for non-subscribers, online viewers means I won&#39;t be reading their Books section anymore. It sort of became a good habit for me and something I look forward to on Sunday mornings: as I drink my coffee and enjoy some peace and quietness as the kids are still asleep, I enjoy catching up with the latest books and reviews. This weekend ritual usually ends with a trip down to the public library with the whole family.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
