<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wordpress on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/wordpress/</link>
    <description>Recent content in wordpress on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/wordpress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to import WordPress XML files</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/how-to-import-wordpress-xml-files-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/how-to-import-wordpress-xml-files-/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip; or, how I brought an old python code back from the dead!
Inspired by Kenneth Reitz&#39;s recent post and spurred by recent events, I decided to turn an old python code I wrote a while back into something that can be (hopefully) easier to get to than by sheer luck.
I&amp;rsquo;m talking about ChoppedPress, my script that let&amp;rsquo;s you split WordPress exported XML files into smaller files that can be easily imported into new WordPress installations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desculpe Pela Bagunça...</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/desculpe-pela-bagunca-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/desculpe-pela-bagunca-/</guid>
      <description>Recentemente eu comecei o processo de migrar o meu blog para o Tumblr, e ao importar os posts antigos do WordPress eu sem querer iniciei uma enxurrada onde certos agregadores estão mostrando posts de 2007&amp;hellip; Ontem eu também causei um problema similar no Twitter e Facebook&amp;hellip;
Por favor aceite os meus mais sinceros pedidos de desculpas pelo incoveniente&amp;hellip; depois escrevo mais sobre a migração para o Tumblr!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sorry for the noise...</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/sorry-for-the-noise-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/sorry-for-the-noise-/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve just recently started migrating my blog to Tumblr, and in the process of importing my archives from WordPress I seem to have caused some issues with certain aggregators that are now picking up posts from 2007&amp;hellip; Yesterday I also triggered a massive torrent on both Twitter and Facebook&amp;hellip;
Please accept my apologies for the incovenience&amp;hellip; more on the Tumblr migration to follow!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
