<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>linux world expo on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</title>
    <link>https://omaciel.github.io/tags/linux-world-expo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in linux world expo on Og Maciel&#39;s Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omaciel.github.io/tags/linux-world-expo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Linux World Expo 2005</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/linux-world-expo-2005-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/linux-world-expo-2005-/</guid>
      <description>So here I am standing in front of the Gnome booth. Vinny and I got here around 1-1:30pm thanks to his awsome navigational skills but were able to see every single booth. The environment was very laid back and not as &amp;ldquo;corporate&amp;rdquo; as last year&amp;rsquo;s event in NYC. We managed to ask a few questions, got a lot of cool stuff, even a complementary made-in-front-of-you latte&#39; at the CA&amp;rsquo;s booth, and just enjoyed it all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux World Expo Bound</title>
      <link>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/linux-world-expo-bound-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omaciel.github.io/posts/linux-world-expo-bound-/</guid>
      <description>So here I am, counting the minutes until I get the hell out of work and head down to Laguardia Airport where I&amp;rsquo;ll be boarding my plane to Boston. My friend Vinny is picking me up for what seems to be a great weekend of geekness. Tomorrow we&amp;rsquo;re going to check out the exhibition floor at this year&amp;rsquo;s Linux World Expo, Boston Edition. I&amp;rsquo;m very excited about this for I will be there with my good friend&amp;hellip; Have you ever been to some type of event (it could be softball) that you really enjoy but in the company of someone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t really like it and only accompanied you after putting up with weeks of you begging him/her to go with you?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
